{"Topic": "Companies and Brands", "Subject": "General Knowledge", "Data": [{"Question": "How many companies are there in BSE Sensex?", "op1": "25", "op2": "30", "op3": "50", "op4": "100", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Volkswagen is a company based in -", "op1": "Germany", "op2": "Sweden", "op3": "France", "op4": "Russia", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Vitara Brezza is a car model launched by \u2013", "op1": "Hyundai", "op2": "Honda", "op3": "Maruti", "op4": "Ford", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "With which company is Sundar Pichai associated?", "op1": "Amazon", "op2": "Microsoft", "op3": "Google", "op4": "Yahoo", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Lava International is a mobile phone company based in -", "op1": "China", "op2": "South Korea", "op3": "Taiwan", "op4": "India", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Nike is a multinational company with its headquarters in \u2013", "op1": "France", "op2": "Germany", "op3": "U.S.A.", "op4": "Sweden", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which company manufactures Pixel brand of mobile phones?", "op1": "Google", "op2": "Microsoft", "op3": "Amazon", "op4": "Motorola", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Sachin Bansal and Binny Bansal are associated with \u2013", "op1": "PayTM", "op2": "Ola Cabs", "op3": "Snapdeal", "op4": "Flipkart", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "TAG Heuer is a famous brand of \u2013", "op1": "Watches", "op2": "Cars", "op3": "Jeans", "op4": "Pens", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": ". Sunil Bharti Mittal is associated with which of the following companies?", "op1": "Airtel", "op2": "Vodafone", "op3": "Telenor", "op4": "Idea", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Ignis is the latest model of car launched by \u2013", "op1": "Hyundai", "op2": "Maruti", "op3": "Toyota", "op4": "Ford", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "The founder of Paytm is \u2013", "op1": "Vijay Shekhar Sharma", "op2": "Jack Ma", "op3": "Sachin Bansal", "op4": "Phanindra Sharma", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Peugeot is a car manufacturing company with its headquarters in", "op1": "France", "op2": "Italy", "op3": "Germany", "op4": "Sweden", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Favre Leuba is a famous brand of \u2013", "op1": "Cars", "op2": "Shoes", "op3": "Cosmetics", "op4": "Watches", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Ferrari is a sports car manufacturer based in \u2013", "op1": "Germany", "op2": "Italy", "op3": "Sweden", "op4": "France", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which motorcycle company has used metal from INS Vikrant to manufacture one of its models?", "op1": "Hero", "op2": "Bajaj", "op3": "TVS", "op4": "Honda", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Qantas Airlines is based in which country?", "op1": "Russia", "op2": "Australia", "op3": "Germany", "op4": "France", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "The headquarters of Amazon company are located in \u2013", "op1": "California", "op2": "Seattle", "op3": "New York", "op4": "Detroit", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "RACEMO Sports Car was recently unveiled by \u2013", "op1": "Maruti Suzuki", "op2": "Toyota", "op3": "Hyundai", "op4": "Tata Motors", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Xiaomi is a smartphone manufacturer based in \u2013", "op1": "China", "op2": "South Korea", "op3": "Taiwan", "op4": "Japan", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Who is the founder of space transport services company, SpaceX?", "op1": "Jeff Bezos", "op2": "Elon Musk", "op3": "Evan Spiegel", "op4": "Jack Dorsey", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "With which of the following companies is Karshanbhai Patel associated?", "op1": "Nirma", "op2": "Hindalco", "op3": "Lupin", "op4": "Essar", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "C in FMCG (with respect to companies) stands for?", "op1": "Cosmetic", "op2": "Consumer", "op3": "Competitive", "op4": "Cheap", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Redmi is a model of smartphone manufactured by \u2013", "op1": "Xiaomi", "op2": "Sony", "op3": "Apple", "op4": "Blackberry", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Radhakishan Damani is the founder of which company?", "op1": "Big Bazar", "op2": "Spencers", "op3": "Foodworld", "op4": "DMart", "Answer": 2}]}